arnhem.co 2016-12-23

# Privacy & Security - Arnhem Clothing

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * _To personalise your experience:_ Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * _To improve our website:_ We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  * _To improve customer service:_ Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 
  * _To process transactions:_ Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Arnhem may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, without notice to you. 

##### Size Charts

### How To Measure:

**Bust**  
Measure under your arms at the fuller part of your bust. Keep tape level across shoulder blades.

**Natural Waist**  
Measure around your natural waistline, keeping the tape comfortably loose.

**Drop Waist**  
Measure 1 1/2 inches below your natural waistline.

**Hips**  
Stand with your feet together and measure around the fullest part of your hips.

**GARMENT SIZE CHART** |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |  |   
  | **6** | **8** | **10** | **12** | **14** |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
AUSTRALIA / NZ | 6 | 8 | 10 | 12 | 14 |   
USA | 2 | 4 | 6 | 8 | 10 |   
UK | 6 | 8 | 10 | 12 | 14 |   
EUROPE | 34 | 36 | 38 | 40 | 42 |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
**STANDARD BODY MEASUREMENTS** |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
  | **6** | **8** | **10** | **12** | **14** |   
BUST (CM) | 80 | 85 | 90 | 95 | 100 |   
WAIST (CM) | 60 | 65 | 70 | 75 | 80 |   
HIP (CM) | 90 | 92 | 97 | 102 | 107 |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
**SHOE SIZE CHART** |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
  | **36** | **37** | **38** | **39** | **40** | **41**  
AU / US | 5 | 6 | 7 | 8 | 9 | 10  
UK | 3 | 4 | 5 | 6 | 7 | 8  
EUROPE | 36 | 37 | 38 | 39 | 40 | 41  
LENGTH CM | 22 | 23 | 24 | 25 | 26 | 27  
|  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
**ARNHEM CHILD** |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |   
  | **1** | **2** | **3** | **4** | **5** |   
AUS/NZ | 1 yrs | 2 yrs | 3 yrs | 4 yrs | 5 yrs |   
USA | 18-24mths | 24mths | 2T | 4T | 5T |   
UK | 12-18mths | 24mths | 2-3 yrs | 3-4 yrs | 4-5 yrs |   
EUROPE | 80-86cm | 86-92cm | 92-98cm | 98-104cm | 104-110cm |
